If you come to the States, it is hard to
find a hard worker and smart people like
you, but the key problem is a lot of
Koreans are too humble. They limit their
potential. If you just stick with that
attitude, you cannot do nothing.
>> I'm in San Francisco at EO House where
entrepreneurs are living together and
doing amazing things. Today, I'm going
to ask some of them to give me their
best elevator pitch in 1 minute.
Can you introduce yourself?
>> Yeah, my name is G.
>> Can you give me your best elevator pitch
in 1 minute?
>> Sure. So, I'm actually a founder of
ScanMyPill. ScanMyPill is basically we
are helping caregivers out there
to help their loved ones taking care of
medication. So, I started this problem
back in like last year of August and
realized that my grandpa went to ER
twice last year because of medication
problems. And because of medication
problem, I was like there must be a
better way to solve this problem. So,
what I've done is create ScanMyPill.
It's a iOS app. And what it does is you
scan the pill and it generates all the
digitization. And after you digitize all
the medication, it could check the
interaction. It could also remind you.
And this helps because they're going to
the doctor is going to ask, "Hey, what
kind of medication you on?" You'll be
able to answer right away and you'll
have logs so that you'll be able to
answer also the question the doctor
asked, "When did you take it? When did
you take it out?" So, that's like the
ScanMyPill the gist of it. And yeah, I'm
helping the 1.5 million people out there
who goes to ER every year. So, I'm
trying to reduce that number.
>> That's incredible. So, people can find
you on the App Store?
>> Yes, iOS app.
>> ScanMyPill.
>> Download it, guys.
>> Hi, so my name is Jordan and I'm the
founder of VisCom. Okay, so a lot of
people don't realize that the world
around us started out as drawings. So,
we kind of help people turn their
drawings into physical products, right?
So, imagine, you know, things that stay
on your screen, we allow people to
essentially hold their ideas, right? So,
going from paper to production.
So, you have a drawing of a shoe, you
want to see that shoe be made in the
real world, we kind of build tools to
accelerate that process. So,
yeah, basically allowing people to hold
their ideas. Great. Awesome.
>> That's incredible. Who are you
targeting? Can I ask that?
>> I would say like kind of people that are
designing things in the physical world,
right? So, like cars, shoes, different
kind of furniture,
things of that nature, right? Anything
that has to eventually become real,
right? I think, you know, as visual
fidelity no longer becomes the signal of
effort, you got to ask yourself what's
like, okay, well, then where does the
signal go? And it goes into the real
world. It's like, okay, not how
realistic can you make it look, but how
real can you actually make the object?
So, we kind of build tools that help
people make their things actually
physical. So, yeah.
>> That's awesome. Thank you very much.
>> My name is Songman Cho. I'm from Korea.
I'm making a game, AI native game, to
teach kids how to use AI.
I've been doing some things in the AI
field. I used to be an AI researcher in
the Intel and then Seoul National Seoul
Asan Medical Center.
And I was really wondering how to teach
the kids
how to use AI, how to leverage AI.
Because the especially in the Bay Area,
the parents they got so much FOMO from
the AI because their peers laid off from
the AI because of the AI. So, I decided
to make a game, and then that game helps
to
teach kids how to
how to use AI. So, there are big
problems in there, and then they should
ask some question to the MPCs. The every
MPC in there, they're AI agent.
So, by doing some questions and then
getting answered that they can leverage
their yeah, talent.
>> My name is George and I'm from China.
I'm currently an entrepreneur in the AI
for education sector. Um so, I'm
currently building an AI voice dictation
tool plus um AI education tool. So, it
happens in your workflow and it is not a
stand-alone learning. I have a message
for those uh non-native speakers who are
entering into the US market either want
to find a job here or looking into
settling into the US market. So, have
you ever had challenges in terms of uh
like making yourself feel professional
when communicating with others like
either you are speaking or sending
messages? We have a tool here to help
you to send effective professional
messages in English. You can either
speak in English or speak in your mother
tongue and you will get ready to send
English. And afterwards, you may also
practice the exact sentences that you
spoke for pronunciation, word choice,
and communication skills that would help
you to succeed in the US market. So, we
are building Ella flow. Hope you could
enjoy it.
>> Wow! You nailed it. Good job!
>> [screaming]
>> Hey, I'm KJ from Tokyo. Very nice to
meet you guys. I'm making a new social
consumer app for the teenager in US. Um
it's a anonymous app and voting who is
the best uh person in this class or who
is the funniest person in this class.
So, everybody adds a voice note, voice
memo, and the the voice turn to be very
funny. As like a "You look
super cute." Or something like that. And
yeah, try to make someone fun. Cuz
uh I have
the 13-years-old daughter and that will
go to New York,
uh from this September. So, I try to
make that app, try to make her
um smile even
far from Tokyo, far from San Francisco.
So, yeah, that's why I'm making this new
Next Bio app for teenagers.
>> That's really cool. Would you say it's
for entertainment purposes then?
>> Yeah, try to make a people fun with the
alternative new communication layer, not
regular Leo, but like anonymous for
entertainment.
>> Awesome.
>> [snorts]
>> Can you introduce yourself?
>> Uh hi, I'm founder of E O. My name is
Tae Young Kim. Nice to meet you.
>> Can you tell me a little bit more about
E O House?
>> E O House is our corporate hacker house.
Hacker house is a founder house. In
here, over 10 founders are living
together, working together, building
something together that can change the
world.
>> You have so many smart and talented
people here, including yourself.
>> Thank you.
>> We just heard a lot of elevator pitches.
How do people come to find E O House?
>> Uh it's a only referral based. Uh people
already knew me or our alumni can
recommend other founders. So, it's very
exclusive community. Only the founders
who bet their life to build something
can join our community.
>> What inspired you to kind of start E O
House?
>> Uh to be honest, to save money. Uh
Silicon Valley is the heart of world
tech innovation, but it is a brutally
expensive. So,
uh a lot of immigrant founders uh come
to the states, but if you want to one
bedroom, uh it costs us like over
$4,000, $3,000, so. Uh it looks
gorgeous, but if you imagine living 16
people in in this uh hacker house is uh
really messy. Yeah. [laughter]
>> But, I think it's really cool that
you're giving people opportunities, like
you said, people who might not have
money but have great ideas. Is there
anything else you want people to know
about EO house?
>> Uh I'm a super uh Korean Korean, so I
only grew up uh in South Korea, and if
you watch this video, my English is not
that good, but I just came uh here 2
years ago to build a global company
because, you know, especially due to AI,
world is getting small uh much much
smaller. So, uh if you [snorts] run your
business, but if you don't uh build
global company from day one, yeah, you
will lose your competence. So, yeah, I
came here, and I wanted to inspire more
young people to build uh something
global because, you know, Koreans are
super smart, and they work hard. If you
uh come to the States, it is hard to
find a hard worker and smart people like
you, but the key problem is a lot of
Koreans are too humble. They limit their
potential. Asian culture uh is uh very
introverted, but if you just stick with
that attitude, uh yeah, you cannot do
nothing.
>> Can you give people one piece of advice?
A lot of the subscribers are trying to
learn English, maybe business English,
wanting to live and work in the US. Any
advice you can give them?
>> English is important, but more than
that, uh if someone gives you
opportunity, yeah, you should pay back.
So, yeah, credit and building trust is
the most important thing uh in business
and career development. So, uh if your
uh language is limited, I think uh it is
okay. And also, it takes time to uh make
it better, but if you lose your uh
credit and trust, your client and your
boss will never hire you and never give
you uh additional opportunities. So, if
you can bring uh good outcome, even
though your English is limited, they
will give you better opportunities.
>> Excellent advice.
>> Yeah.
>> Just go for it.
>> Yeah, just go for it. I started learning
English when I was uh 30, so it's uh
quite late and I wasn't a good student
in high school and middle school and
even yeah, in college. But, I think the
best way to improve your English is
yeah, you should know why learning
English matters. And second is just uh
change your environment. I watched the
Tyler Tyler's video how to
improve your English best. Yeah, you
should change people you meet and your
environment. For example, you shouldn't
watch uh Korean contents for a while and
also if someone send you Kakao message
in Korean, you just should reply it in
English. Your friends will blame you,
but just do it. Don't speak Korean for a
while. But, without knowing why it is
hard to
execute. So, yeah, having your own why
is the most important thing.
>> Thank you so much.
>> Yeah, thank you.